As your computer gets older, I'm sure you've "cum", accumulated a lot of files, so you're going to have to start deleting some of those files.
Hi, I'm Charles Stewart Jr., and I'm going to show you how to delete a file.
We're going to use, we're going to, you work with a Microsoft Windows XP, because that's pretty much what's out there in the world today.
What's cool about Microsoft is they, they "ha", they have three ways to do everything.
So, when you want to delete something, there's three ways you can do it.
One, would just be to highlight it, and then hit the delete key, and it'll ask you if you want to delete it.
Or you can take it, right click, and then delete it.
Or, you can just drag it into the garbage can, or the recycle bin as they call it.
And there you go, it's pretty simple.
And that's again, how Microsoft does pretty much everything.
You'll find, as you start to look at Windows, that they usually offer three ways to do everything, which is really cool.
So, all in all, that's how to delete a file.